manulife financial corporation is a
canadian multinational insurance company
and financial services provider
headquartered in toronto ontario
the company operates in canada and asia
as manulife and in the united states
primarily through its john hancock
financial division
manulife at one point serviced over 26
million customers worldwide
here are some more informations about
this
insurance company
it's formally named
type traded as industry
founded
headquarters
key people
products
revenue
net income
aum
total assets
total equity
number of employees
subsidiaries and its website which is
www www.manulife.com